Guide to the Deep Dish TV Records MSS.312
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I. Video Productions, 1982-2018; 13.5 Linear Feet in 17 manuscript boxes and 5 flat boxes; 906 MiniDV; 470 U-matic; 93 1_Inch_Video_Reel; 81 Betacam_SP; 26 Betacam; 58 DVCAM; 27 VHS; 5 Hi8; 3 audiocassettes; 1.538 Terabytes in 6,117 files
  - Ideas and Power, Circa 1991 (Box 145, Minidv 312_0789, Box 146, Minidv 312_0834)
  - Ideas and Power -- "Lucha Libre: Super Barrio", June 21, 1991; cuid39337 (Box 98, U-matic 312_0264, Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_60)
  - Behind Censorship: The Assault on Civil Liberties -- Production File, 1990-1992 (Box 4, Folder 10, 11)
  - Behind Censorship: The Assault on Civil Liberties -- Entry and License Agreements, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Behind Censorship: The Assault on Civil Liberties -- "Women's Alternative Ways" -- Distribution Agreements, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Behind Censorship: The Assault on Civil Liberties -- "Women's Alternative Ways", May 14, 1991 (Box 172, 1 inch video reel 312_0179, Box 312_1873, 1 inch video reel 312_1873)
    312_1873 also includes a PSA.
  - Behind Censorship: The Assault on Civil Liberties -- "State of the Art: Art of the State?", May 21-23, 1991; cuid39334 (Box 99, U-matic 312_0267, Box 146, Minidv 312_0796, Box 312_1849, 1 inch video reel 312_1849, Box 312_1861, 1 inch video reel 312_1861, Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_48)
    312_1849 includes a PSA.
  - Behind Censorship: The Assault on Civil Liberties -- Compilation Tape, Circa 1991 (Box 143, Minidv 312_0655)
    This tape includes "State of the Art: Art of the State" and "Vibrant Voices: People of Color Speak Out"
  - Behind Censorship: The Assault on Civil Liberties -- "Access Denied", May 28-30, 1991 (Box 99, U-matic 312_0266, Box 145, Minidv 312_0735)
  - Behind Censorship: The Assault on Civil Liberties -- "Anchors Away", May 28-30, 1991 (Box 98, U-matic 312_0263, Box 135, U-matic 312_1393)
  - Behind Censorship: The Assault on Civil Liberties -- Compilation Tapes, May 28, 1991 (Box 146, Minidv 312_0795, Box 168, 1 inch video reel 312_0167)
    These tapes include "Access Denied" and "Anchors Away!" 312_0167 also includes a PSA.
  - Behind Censorship: The Assault on Civil Liberties -- "Political Prisoners in the U.S.", June 1, 1991; cuid39330 (Box 98, U-matic 312_0261, Box 144, Minidv 312_0664, 312_0696, Box 146, Minidv 312_0792, Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_45)
  - Behind Censorship: The Assault on Civil Liberties -- "In Other Words: The Struggle Over Language", June 4-6, 1991; cuid39335 (Box 85, U-matic 312_0070, Box 98, U-matic 312_0262, Box 146, Minidv 312_0793, 312_0794, Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_47)
    Coordinated by Annie Goldson and LGTV
  - Behind Censorship: The Assault on Civil Liberties -- Compilation Tape, June 9, 1991 (Box 175, 1 inch video reel 312_0188)
    This tape includes "Can't Jail the Revolution!," "Political Prisoners in the US," and "Break the Walls Down! Free All PPs and POWs in the US." It also includes a PSA.
  - Behind Censorship: The Assault on Civil Liberties -- "Forbidden Fruit Fight Back", June 18-20, 1991; cuid39336 (Box 103, U-matic 312_0314, Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_46)
    Coordinated by Valda Lewis
  - Behind Censorship: The Assault on Civil Liberties -- "Who Owns This Body?" -- Entry and License Agreements, Spring 1991 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Behind Censorship: The Assault on Civil Liberties -- "Who Owns This Body?", June 18-20, 1991 (Box 103, U-matic 312_0316, Box 144, Minidv 312_0709)
  - Behind Censorship: The Assault on Civil Liberties -- Compilation Tapes, June 18-20, 1991 (Box 103, U-matic 312_0315, Box 146, Minidv 312_0807, Box 175, 1 inch video reel 312_0187)
    These tapes include "Who Owns This Body?" and "Forbidden Fruit Fight Back."
  - Behind Censorship: The Assault on Civil Liberties -- "Vibrant Voices: People of Color Speak Out", June 25-27, 1991; cuid39338 (Box 84, U-matic 312_0063, Box 104, U-matic 312_0317, Box 144, Minidv 312_0713, Box 146, Minidv 312_0806, Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_49)
  - Behind Censorship: The Assault on Civil Liberties -- "Mutiny on the Corporate Sponsor Ship", July 2-4, 1991 (Box 104, U-matic 312_0318, Box 146, Minidv 312_0805, Box 312_1855, 1 inch video reel 312_1855)
  - Behind Censorship: The Assault on Civil Liberties -- "Can't Jail the Revolution!", circa 1991; cuid39421 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_44)
  - Videotape Labels, circa 1990-2011 (Box 5, Folder 2, Box 74, Folder 1)
  - Celebrating 20 Years of Public Access Television -- Production File, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Celebrating 20 Years of Public Access Television -- "Voices of Democracy", October 3, 1991; cuid39339 (Box 102, U-matic 312_0299, Box 146, Minidv 312_0804, Box 169, 1 inch video reel 312_0169, Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_58)
    Coordinated by NFLCP and NAMAC
  - Celebrating 20 Years of Public Access Television -- "Teaching TV: Video Production in the Schools", October 8-10, 1991 (Box 104, U-matic 312_0319, Box 146, Minidv 312_0803, Box 312_1854, 1 inch video reel 312_1854)
    Coordinated by Chris Bratton
  - Celebrating 20 Years of Public Access Television -- "Fear of Disclosure: Mujeres Latinas", October 15-17, 1991 (Box 100, U-matic 312_0283)
    Coordinated by Marina Alvarez and Ellen Spiro
  - Celebrating 20 Years of Public Access Television -- "Fear of Disclosure: Mujeres Latinas" -- Distribution Agreement, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Celebrating 20 Years of Public Access Television -- "Black Women, Sexual Politics and the Revolution" -- Production File, 1991; cuid39280 (Box 5, Folder 4, Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_50)
  - Celebrating 20 Years of Public Access Television -- "Invisible Women", circa 1991; cuid39422 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_53)
  - Celebrating 20 Years of Public Access Television -- Compilation Tapes, October 15-17, 1991 (Box 99, U-matic 312_0269, Box 126, U-matic 312_0556, Box 174, 1 inch video reel 312_0186)
    These tapes include "Black Women, Sexual Politics and the Revolution" coordinated by Cyrille Phipps and Michelle McKenzie of Not Channel Zero; "Fear of Disclosure: Mujeres Latinas" coordinated by Marina Alvarez and Ellen Spiro; and a PSA.
  - Celebrating 20 Years of Public Access Television -- Compilation Tape, Circa 1991 (Box 146, Minidv 312_0816)
    This tape includes "Black Women, Sexual Politics, and the Revolution" and "Invisible Women."
  - Celebrating 20 Years of Public Access Television -- "Idiot Box Savant", October 29-31, 1991; cuid39340 (Box 100, U-matic 312_0281, Box 176, 1 inch video reel 312_0192, Box 145, Minidv 312_0758, Box 146, Minidv 312_0814, Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_52)
    Coordinated by Erin O'Meara with 1*4*ALL; 312_0192 also includes a PSA.
  - Celebrating 20 Years of Public Access Television -- "Unbalancing the News" -- Production File, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Celebrating 20 Years of Public Access Television -- "Unbalancing the News", November 5-7, 1991; cuid39341 (Box 100, U-matic 312_0280, Box 144, Minidv 312_0714, Box 146, Minidv 312_0813, Box 177, 1 inch video reel 312_0193, Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_57)
    Coordinated by Barbara Lattanzi; 312_0193 also includes a PSA.
  - Celebrating 20 Years of Public Access Television -- "No More War Toys", November 12 - 14, 1991; cuid39343 (Box 82, U-matic 312_0044, 312_0045, Box 100, U-matic 312_0279, Box 146, Minidv 312_0819, Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_54)
  - Celebrating 20 Years of Public Access Television -- "Community Visions: From Victim to Survivor", Circa 1991; cuid39331 (Box 146, Minidv 312_0815, Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_51)
  - Celebrating 20 Years of Public Access Television -- Compilation Tapes, October 22-24, 1991 (Box 100, U-matic 312_0282, Box 312_1857, 1 inch video reel 312_1857)
    These tapes include "Community Visions: From Victim to Survivor" coordinated by Margie Strosser with W.O.A.R. and "Peace At Home" coordinated by Women Against Abuse Legal Center and Community Legal Services
  - Celebrating 20 Years of Public Access Television -- "We Interrupt This Schedule: Day Without Art" World AIDS Day Presentation, December 1-3, 1991; cuid39348 (Box 82, U-matic 312_0046, Box 83, U-matic 312_0047, 312_0048, Box 89, U-matic 312_0114, Box 100, U-matic 312_0278, Box 106, U-matic 312_0338, Box 120, U-matic 312_0491, Box 145, Minidv 312_0724, Box 146, Minidv 312_0818, Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_59)
    Produced by The Kitchen and Borough of Manhattan Community College. The title of this program is sometimes recorded as "We Interrupt This Program: Day Without Art."
  - Celebrating 20 Years of Public Access Television -- "Teaching TV", circa 1991; cuid39423 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_55)
  - Celebrating 20 Years of Public Access Television -- "Thieves of Time", circa 1991; cuid39424 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_56)
  - Paper Tiger Newstand Submaster, October 22, 1991 (Box 135, U-matic 312_1388)
    From Fiona's 8mm Footage Repeated
  - "Bicentennial," "Soap Opera Magazine", December 10, 1991 (Box 312_1852, 1 inch video reel 312_1852)
  - "El Mozote, 10th Aniversario I", December 11, 1991 (Box 132, U-matic 312_0979)
    Contents include 10 month anniversary of the Masacre del Mozote, march and vigil
  - "Out of the Blue", circa 1991 (Box 129, Vhs 312_0592)
    With Richard Fung
  - "Howard Koch - You Must Remember This", Circa 1991 (Box 136, U-matic 312_1396)
    Cambiz A Khozravi
  - "Media Wilder" -- Production File, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - "Summa 91" -- Production File, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - ROAR! A Paper Tiger TV Mini Retrospective -- "Herb Schiller reads the New York Times", November 19-21, 1991; cuid39345 (Box 83, U-matic 312_0051, Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_62)
  - ROAR! A Paper Tiger TV Mini Retrospective -- "Operation Storm the Media", November 19-21, 1991; cuid39344 (Box 83, U-matic 312_0049, Box 136, U-matic 312_1405, Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_64)
    U-matic tape 312_1405 was identified as moldy by the Media Preservation Unit. This item is currently isolated from other items in a polyethylene bag with a desiccated board and RH monitor strip. If this strip indicates an RH greater than 50%, the Preservation department should be contacted ASAP. Do not open this packaging without contacting the Preservation Department.
  - ROAR! A Paper Tiger TV Mini Retrospective -- Compilation Tapes, November 19-21, 1991 (Box 83, U-matic 312_0050, Box 146, Minidv 312_0817)
    These tapes include "Operation Storm the Media" and "Herb Schiller Reads the New York Times."
  - ROAR! A Paper Tiger TV Mini Retrospective -- "Born to be Sold: The Strange Case of Baby M/S", November 26-28, 1991; cuid39347 (Box 100, U-matic 312_0276, Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_61)
    Produced by Paper Tiger TV
  - ROAR! A Paper Tiger TV Mini Retrospective -- "Transformer AIDS", November 26-28, 1991; cuid39346 (Box 99, U-matic 312_0271, Box 145, Minidv 312_0757, Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_68)
    Produced by Paper Tiger Southwest
  - ROAR! A Paper Tiger TV Mini Retrospective -- Compilation Tapes, November 26-28, 1991 (Box 100, U-matic 312_0277, Box 126, Betacam sp 312_0558, Box 146, Minidv 312_0822, Box 312_1851, 1 inch video reel 312_1851, Box 312_1853, 1 inch video reel 312_1853)
    These tapes include "Born to be Sold: The Strange Case of Baby M/S," "Transformer AIDS" produced by Paper Tiger TV and Paper Tiger Southwest, and "Revolution in a Box: What a Crock!"
  - ROAR! A Paper Tiger TV Mini Retrospective -- "Renee Tajima Reads Asian Images in American Film", December 3-5, 1991; cuid39349 (Box 99, U-matic 312_0274, Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_65)
  - ROAR! A Paper Tiger TV Mini Retrospective -- Compilation Tapes, December 3-5, 1991 (Box 99, U-matic 312_0270, 312_0273, Box 146, Minidv 312_0820, Box 171, 1 inch video reel 312_0175, 312_0176)
    These tapes include "Torn Between Colors: Black Media, Asian Images," "Renee Tajima Reads Asian Images," and "Alternative Media in the Bay Area" produced by Paper Tiger TV West. 312_0176 also includes a PSA.
  - ROAR! A Paper Tiger TV Mini Retrospective -- "The Bicentennial Will Not Be Televised", December 10-12, 1991; cuid39350 (Box 99, U-matic 312_0272, Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_66)
  - ROAR! A Paper Tiger TV Mini Retrospective -- "Judith Mayne Dials Through Daytime Soap", December 10-12, 1991; cuid39351 (Box 100, U-matic 312_0284, Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_63)
    Produced by Paper Tiger TV with ACTV Columbus OH
  - ROAR! A Paper Tiger TV Mini Retrospective -- Compilation Tapes, December 10-12, 1991 (Box 98, U-matic 312_0260, Box 146, Minidv 312_0821, Box 312_0775, 1 inch video reel 312_0775)
    These tapes include "The Bicentennial Will Not Be Televised" produced by Paper Tiger TV and "Judith Mayne Dials Through Daytime Soap Operas" produced by Paper Tiger TV and ACTV (Columbus, OH).
  - ROAR! A Paper Tiger TV Mini Retrospective -- Compilation Tapes, December 17-19, 1991 (Box 101, U-matic 312_0291, 312_0292, Box 143, Minidv 312_0657, Box 145, Minidv 312_0764, Box 312_0774, 1 inch video reel 312_0774, Box 312_0780, 1 inch video reel 312_0780)
    These tapes include "Brian Winston Reads the TV News: Live and On Tape" and "Unpacking Ted Koppel's Revolution in a Box" produced by Paper Tiger TV, John Walden, Paper Tiger Reads Columbus Media, and ACTV. 312_0780 also includes a PSA.
  - ROAR! A Paper Tiger TV Mini Retrospective -- "Paper Tiger Reads Columbus Media", December 17-19, 1991 (Box 101, U-matic 312_0294)
    Produced by PTTV with ACTV
  - ROAR! A Paper Tiger TV Mini Retrospective -- "Torn Between Colors", 1991; cuid39425 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_67)
  - Not Channel Zero -- Production File -- Black Planet Productions, 1991-1997 (Box 5, Folder 10, 11)
  - "Not Channel Zero Goes to War" Production File -- Black Planet Productions, circa 1991-1997 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - TV News on L.A. Riots, January 8, 1992 (Box 129, U-matic 312_0582)
    B-Roll "Cuba Rough Cut Youth Section" and "David on 'Slavery' up to Bobby on 'Carrying the revolution inside youth'"
  - Jordan Interviews, January 21, 1992 (Box 135, U-matic 312_1120)
    Content includes Helen Rodriguez-Tores, Pediatrician and Faye Williams, Congressional Causes
  - Unheard Voices -- "Women and Discovery: 8th International Women's Day Video Festival," Program 1: "Women's Empowerment", March 31 - April 2, 1992 (Box 101, U-matic 312_0293)
    Coordinated by Ann Bennett
  - Unheard Voices -- "Women and Discovery: 8th International Women's Day Video Festival," Program 2: "Older Women Speak Out / Families", March 31 - April 2, 1992 (Box 102, U-matic 312_0297)
  - Unheard Voices -- "Women and Discovery: 8th International Women's Day Video Festival," Program 3: "Work, Sexual Harassment, and Violence", April 7-9, 1992 (Box 101, U-matic 312_0295)
  - Unheard Voices -- "Women and Discovery: 8th International Women's Day Video Festival," Program 4: "Media and Politics", April 7-9, 1992 (Box 102, U-matic 312_0296)
  - Unheard Voices -- "Women and Discovery: 8th International Women's Day Video Festival," Parts 1 and 2, Mach 31 - April 2, 1992 (Box 145, Minidv 312_0763, Box 312_0776, 1 inch video reel 312_0776, Box 312_0779, 1 inch video reel 312_0779)
    312_0779 also includes a PSA.
  - Unheard Voices -- "Women and Discovery: 8th International Women's Day Video Festival," Parts 3 and 4, April 7, 1992 (Box 312_0778, 1 inch video reel 312_0778, Box 312_0777, 1 inch video reel 312_0777, Box 145, Minidv 312_0761, 312_0762)
    312_0778 also includes a PSA.
  - Unheard Voices -- "Hands Off Cuba! TV Teach-In", May 5-7, 1992 (Box 124, U-matic 312_0530, Box 126, U-matic 312_0559, 312_0560, Box 146, Minidv 312_0801, Box 312_0785, 1 inch video reel 312_0785)
    Coordinated by Che Che Martinez and Cathy Scott with the Hands Off Cuba Video Project; 312_0785 also includes a PSA
  - Unheard Voices -- "Forging Ties For Peace", June 2-4, 1992 (Box 134, U-matic 312_1113, Box 142, U-matic 312_1846, Box 145, Minidv 312_0787)
    Produced by Simone Farkhondeh and Laura Flanders for MADRE
  - Unheard Voices -- "Haiti: Misunderstood Neighbor", June 2-4, 1992 (Box 102, U-matic 312_0298, Box 142, U-matic 312_1847, Box 145, Minidv 312_0788)
    Produced by Ayiti Vizion with Somerville Community Access TV
  - Unheard Voices -- Open / Close, Circa 1992 (Box 172, 1 inch video reel 312_0178)
  - Beyond the Browning of America -- "Expansion, Intervention, and Migration", November 6, 1991 (Box 101, U-matic 312_0288, Box 144, Minidv 312_0698, 312_0704, 312_705, Box 145, Minidv 312_0786)
  - Beyond the Browning of America -- "Work and Opportunity", November 6, 1991; cuid39342 (Box 101, U-matic 312_0286, Box 143, Minidv 312_0653, 312_0658, Box 145, Minidv 312_0767, Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_80)
  - Beyond the Browning of America -- "Culture and Identity", Circa 1992; cuid39352 (Box 144, Minidv 312_0666, Box 146, Minidv 312_0797, Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_81)
  - Beyond the Browning of America -- Program 1, April 14-16, 1992 (Box 101, U-matic 312_0289, Box 312_0769, 1 inch video reel 312_0769, Box 312_1865, 1 inch video reel 312_1865)
    Coordinated by Pedro Rivera and Susan Zeig
  - Beyond the Browning of America -- Program 2, April 21-23, 1992 (Box 99, U-matic 312_0275, Box 312_0768, 1 inch video reel 312_0768, Box 312_1864, 1 inch video reel 312_1864)
  - Beyond the Browning of America -- Program 3, April 28-30, 1992 (Box 100, U-matic 312_0285, Box 312_0770, 1 inch video reel 312_0770, Box 312_1860, 1 inch video reel 312_1860)
  - Siempre Trabajando: Latinos and Labor -- "Justice for Janitors", 1992; cuid39429 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_87)
  - Siempre Trabajando: Latinos and Labor -- "La Historia de Todos Nosotros (The History of All of Us)", 1992; cuid39430 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_88)
  - Siempre Trabajando: Latinos and Labor, "Sin Fronteras: Four Dollars a Day? No Way!", 1992; cuid39431 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_89)
  - Siempre Trabajando: Latinos and Labor -- Program 1, May 12-14, 1992 (Box 101, U-matic 312_0287, Box 146, Minidv 312_0800, Box 312_0771, 1 inch video reel 312_0771, Box 312_1859, 1 inch video reel 312_1859)
    Program One includes the segments "Si, Se Puede!," "Daily News Is Bad News," and "Workers Without A Voice: New Immigrants"
  - Siempre Trabajando: Latinos and Labor -- Program 2, May 19-21, 1992 (Box 105, U-matic 312_0328, Box 144, Minidv 312_0663, Box 146, Minidv 312_0799, Box 312_0772, 1 inch video reel 312_0772, Box 312_1856, 1 inch video reel 312_1856)
    Program Two includes the segments "Our History: La Historia de Todos Nosotros" and "El Paro Va! The Strike Is On!"
    312_0663 tape label notes "tape beeps! don't use. test!!"
  - Siempre Trabajando: Latinos and Labor -- Program 3, May 26-28, 1992 (Box 105, U-matic 312_0327, Box 143, Minidv 312_0654, Box 146, Minidv 312_0798, Box 312_0781, 1 inch video reel 312_0781, Box 312_1858, 1 inch video reel 312_1858)
    Program Three includes the segments "Sin Fronteras," "$4 a Day? No Way!" and "Lucha Libre: Super Barrio"
  - Siempre Trabajando: Latinos and Labor, 1992; cuid39524 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_86)
  - "In Your Own Backyard" -- Production File, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - "How Deep Dish Comes to You" Short -- Transcript and Log, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - "Native Land" -- Production File, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Rock the Boat -- Outreach to Native Americans, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Rock the Boat -- Series Production File, 1992-1993 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Rock the Boat -- Open, circa 1992 (Box 132, Betacam 312_0905)
  - Rock the Boat -- "Hands on the Verdict: The 1992 Los Angeles Uprising" -- Production File (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Rock the Boat -- "Hands On the Verdict: The 1992 Los Angeles Uprising, Part 1: Devastating Blows", September 15-17, 1992; cuid39354 (Box 104, U-matic 312_0322, 312_0324, Box 146, Minidv 312_0802, Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_82)
    Coordinated by Liz Canner and Julia Meltzer with Los Angeles Video Activists (LAVA)
  - Rock the Boat -- "Hands On the Verdict: The 1992 Los Angeles Uprising, Part 2: Sentence of Fire", September 15-17, 1992 (Box 104, U-matic 312_0323, 312_0325)
  - Rock the Boat -- "Hands On the Verdict: The 1992 Los Angeles Uprising," Parts 1 and 2, September 15-17, 1992 (Box 104, U-matic 312_0326, Box 144, Minidv 312_0691, 312_0700, Box 312_0782, 1 inch video reel 312_0782)
    Coordinated by Liz Canner and Julia Meltzer with Los Angeles Video Activists (LAVA); 312_0782 also includes a PSA.
  - Rock the Boat -- "The Nation Erupts" -- Production File, 1992-1993 (Box 7, Folder 2, 3)
  - Rock the Boat -- "The Nation Erupts", September 22-24, 1992 (Box 84, Betacam sp 312_0064, Box 102, U-matic 312_0302, 312_0303, 312_0305, Box 104, U-matic 312_0321, Box 144, Minidv 312_0690, Box 312_0783, 1 inch video reel 312_0783)
    Produced by Not Channel Zero (Black Planet Productions); 312_0783 also includes a PSA.
  - Rock the Boat -- "No Hay Paz" -- Production File, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Rock the Boat -- "No Hay Paz", September 29 - October 1, 1992; cuid39353 (Box 102, U-matic 312_0304, Box 144, Minidv 312_0702, Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_83)
    Produced by Roberto Arevalo with Somerville Community Access TV
  - Rock the Boat -- "Aggression and Self Determination: Massacre in East Timor" -- Production File, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Rock the Boat -- "Aggression and Self Determination: Massacre in East Timor", September 29 - October 1, 1992 (Box 104, U-matic 312_0320, Box 105, U-matic 312_0331)
    Produced by East Timor Action Network
  - Rock the Boat -- Compilation Tapes, September 29 - October 1, 1992 (Box 91, Betacam 312_0135, Box 101, U-matic 312_0290, Box 102, U-matic 312_0300, 312_0301, Box 145, Minidv 312_0730, Box 312_0773, 1 inch video reel 312_0773)
    These tapes include "No Hay Paz" produced by Roberto Arevalo with SCAT and "Aggression and Self-Determination: Massacre in East Timor" produced by East Timor Action Network; 312_0773 also includes a PSA.
  - Rock the Boat -- "Word! Your Voice is a Drum" -- Production File, 1992-1993 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Rock the Boat -- "Word! Your Voice is a Drum", October 6-8, 1992 (Box 105, U-matic 312_0330, 312_0332, 312_0333, 312_0334, 312_0329, Box 90, Betacam 312_0134)
    Coordinated by Anthony Riddle for the Alliance for Community Media
  - Rock the Boat -- "The New Resistance: Southwestern Communities of Color Struggling for Environmental and Economic Justice" -- Production File, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Rock the Boat -- "The New Resistance: Southwestern Communities of Color Struggling for Environmental and Economic Justice", October 13-18, 1992 (Box 125, U-matic 312_0547, Box 140, U-matic 312_1829, Box 145, Minidv 312_0729, Box 312_0441, 1 inch video reel 312_0441)
    Live Call-in Show
  - Rock the Boat -- "Una Historia" -- Production File, 1992-1993 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Rock the Boat -- "Una Historia", October 27-29, 1992 (Box 106, U-matic 312_0337, 312_0341)
    Coordinated by Luis Valdovino and Dan Boord; No intro credits
  - Rock the Boat -- "Puro Party: Celebrating a Genocide" -- Production File, April-September, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Rock the Boat -- "Puro Party: Celebrating a Genocide", October 27-29, 1992 (Box 106, U-matic 312_0339)
    Coordinated by Lizzie Martinez, Brett Littman and Jim Mendiola